Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
[birds chirping]
[banging in distance]
[banging continues]
[lock clicks]
[keys jingling]
[Duane] Jade, I need you
to start on the bathrooms.
Joslyn, can you please
take out all the eggs, batter,
patties and McMuffins
out of the freezer, okay?
I'll help you
once I turn everything on.
[sets down keys]
[singsongy]
Good morning, team.
[women scream]
[Jeffrey]
No, no, no.
Don't be scared.
You just do what I say,
no one gets hurt, okay?
[gasps]
No, no, look.
Pointing it down.
Okay, now,
I'm gonna say a polite
and cheerful "Good morning,"
and then you guys say it back.
Good morning.
No... Duane, after I say it.
That's how that works. Okay?
Now, good morning, team.
[all]
Good morning.
Yes. Perfect.
I say what to do
and you guys just do it. Okay.
I want you to get
your coats back on.
Duane, grab your coat.
[Duane] Huh?
Grab your coat.
I don't have one, sir.
You don't have a coat?
How do you not have a coat?
I just forgot.
[sighs]
Well, you're just gonna
have to be a little cold today.
All right, let's go.
After you. Ladies first.
Now, listen to me.
You guys aren't
gonna die in here.
Soon as I'm out of here,
I'm gonna call the cops
and they're gonna
let you guys out.
Probably get the day off.
No, don't, don't.
Do not look at me like that.
Duane, stop it.
'Cause this is your fault.
It's cold.
Are you serious?
[sighs]
Dang it.
I don't know what kind of jerk
doesn't bring his own coat
to work.
Okay? Happy now?
[Duane]
My ears are cold.
[Jeffrey]
This is the part of the story
where I hope you're wondering
how a nice guy like me
ends up becoming a criminal.
[Scheimreif over speaker]
Hello?
This thing on?
[Jeffrey]
Shit!
[Scheimreif over speaker]
Come on, Duane.
Good morning.
Uh, welcome to McDonald's.
I'm gonna put you on
a brief hold.
[Scheimreif over speaker]
What the hell, Duane?
[Jeffrey]
I can't blame my parents.
I had a good childhood.
I was just never good
at school or behaving.
But I was good
at certain things
that were really valuable
to the military.
But after my discharge,
I didn't know where I fit
or what to do
or how to give my kids
the things that other kids had.
So I made some bad choices
that took away
some other choices.
And those bad choices
all started two years ago
at my daughter's
sixth birthday party.
[happy chatter]
[dog barking]
[Jeffrey] All right,
you got to make a big ol' wish.
[kids chattering]
[girl squeals]
One more.
[scattered clapping]
Did you make a wish?
What'd you wish for?
[Becky] A bike.
Bike?
I don't know if a bike
is exactly gonna fit
into this box, but...
rip it open.
[kids chattering excitedly]
I'm gonna race ya. Yeah.
[chatter quiets]
What do you think?
It's cool, right?
It's my old Erector Set.
[baby babbling]
Let's open it up.
There's 200 pieces in here.
[pieces clattering]
[boy] No!
I mean, you got engines,
you got gears, pulleys,
wheels, lights, switches.
We can make almost anything
that we want with this thing.
Look, anything that you can
dream, we can make it, okay?
Me and you. What do you say?
[kid clears throat]
Can you make a bike
with it?
[noisemaker blows]
[stammers] Yeah.
Yeah.
[Steve]
I can't believe the dude I knew
from the 82nd
can't even afford a bike.
Well, tell me
how you're doing so well.
Well, let me see.
Just this week, I got
two Japanese dudes passports.
That's 5K a pop.
Five grand
for fake passports?
No, for real passports.
Man...
Can I help you with that?
Hell motherfucking no,
you can't.
You can't help me with shit.
[laughs] You crazy, man?
You ain't helping me do
a goddamn thing.
I don't need your help.
Plus, we already know
that doing things the right way
is not your superpower.
Whatever. That's...
Okay, then tell me
what my superpower is, then?
Enlighten me, Buddha.
Mm.
What's the flow rate
on that hose?
12 gallons per minute.
Mm-hmm.
How many houses is
on this street?
Twenty-eight.
And out of those,
how many got chimneys?
Garages?
How many of 'em use a heat pump
instead of a traditional AC?
You want me
to sell HVAC systems
or something? Just...
No, no, man,
I'm trying to make a point.
Then make the point,
please.
Observation.
Details.
You see shit
people don't see.
You got like a little
X-ray vision going on.
What, you think they dropped
you off in Central America
'cause you a good shot?
Is that what you think?
No. No...
No, they dropped you
because of what you see.
Shit, if I had
a brain like yours,
I'd be running
the whole goddamn world.
You know, you the smartest
dumb nigga I ever known.
That shit crazy.
You can stop filling up
that pool now.
Ain't nobody gonna
get in there.
That shit cold as hell.
[laughs]
[Jeffrey] So, Mama
is probably gonna want to know
how the party was, and,
yeah, I think we did our best.
What do you think?
Maybe we don't mention
the pool. [chuckles]
[entry bell jingling]
It's the trying that counts,
right?
[Becky] Mommy!
Hi, birthday girl.
[Jeffrey sighs]
How was your party?
[Becky]
Everybody did their best.
[Talena] Oh. Are you ready
for your other party?
[car door closes]
Hi.
[chuckles]
How are you?
Hey, can I talk to you
for a second?
Real-real quick, real quick.
I know the last few months
haven't been easy,
and we don't have the things
that we actually need,
and that's my fault
and I own that.
Okay? I do, but I-I think
I have it figured out now.
I just got to use
my superpower and
put my brain on what I want.
Your superpower?
Yes.
[scoffs]
I can't do this, Jeff.
Look-- No.
I'm done.
Come on,
please don't do this.
Goodbye.
[car door closes]
[engine starts]
[sighs]
All right, banana head.
Say goodbye.
[Becky]
Love you!
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait!
[Jeffrey]
I didn't blame her
for laughing at me.
For thinking I was a joke.
But there were things
that she didn't know about me.
Things that weren't so funny.
[ladder clattering]
Steve knew
what I was capable of.
I do see things
that other people don't see.
Like right now, I see that kid
climbing up that ladder,
and I know that
under that flimsy roof
is a machine that turns ground
beef and potatoes into money.
[entry bell jingles]
With the same dining room,
the same deep fryers
with blinking red timer lights,
the same shake machine
with the same two flavors
and the same safe full of
weekend corporate burger money
that no one was gonna miss.
They empty that safe
at the exact same time
on Monday morning
at every single McDonald's.
Hi. Welcome to McDonald's.
Do you know what you want?
Huh?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Um, yeah, I figured it out.
Thank you.
[Jeffrey]
There are over 10,000
almost identical McDonald's
across the United States.
Question was:
How many do you need to rob
to get a real house,
buy your kids nice things
and win your family back?
Turns out,
the answer is 45.
[reporter over TV]
The Roofman has struck again,
cutting a hole through the roof
of this McDonald's
at the corner of Madison
and Jewell in Fayetteville.
As you can imagine, this was
a terrifying experience.
[Duane over TV] He came in,
threw us in the freezer
and gave me his coat.
He gave you his coat?
Yes.
Uh, yeah,
he didn't want me to be cold.
He was actually
really nice.
[reporter] Police believe
this is the same suspect
who has been terrorizing
our local community
with 45 incidents...
Mm.
...this past year alone.
We have a sketch
of the Roofman.
He is always
wearing a mask.
He's described
as six-foot-two
with an athletic build.
What?
The Roofman has also struck
Burger King,
Kentucky Fried Chicken...
Nice TV you got here, Jeff.
Big.
How you afford
something like that?
We got 15 hungry kids
out there
that are
losing their minds
for cake.
We got to go.
[TV volume increases]
[reporter] ...all of
these brazen incidents...
We got to go.
Hold on, hold on.
We got to go
right now.
Let me see...
If she doesn't
get her presents
right now...
I want to know what's going on
with the damn suspect.
...she's gonna
lose her mind.
Can I see?
All right.
Why you turning it off?
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait.
Don't, don't, don't, d--
[groans]
Come on.
Let's go.
Goddamn, man.
[mariachi band playing
lively music]
[playing "Happy Birthday"]
[band and guests]
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday ♪
♪ To you ♪
♪ Happy birthday, bandida ♪
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
You.
[song continues
with lyrics in Spanish]
[whoops]
[song ends]
[cheering]
[whistling]
Let's go!
All right.
Big breath, big wish.
Here we go.
[cheering loudly]
All right, we're gonna do
this one first this year.
Big things
in little boxes.
[Becky]
What is this?
A garage door opener?
Why'd you give me
a garage door opener?
I don't know.
I just couldn't think
of anywhere else
to put, uh,
the saber-toothed tiger,
so...
I don't know. I couldn't put it
in the kitchen, could I?
[whispering]
So, where is it?
[band playing "El Fuereño"]
[cheering]
[band continues playing]
You're the best daddy
in the whole entire world!
[laughing]
Now, go ahead, get on it.
[vehicles approaching]
[Becky]
I love it.
[tires screech]
[siren chirps]
[bicycle bell jingles]
[indistinct
police radio chatter]
How you guys doing?
We're looking
for Jeffrey Manchester.
This about the registration?
Yeah, I got it
right in here.
One second.
["El Fuereño" continues
with lyrics in Spanish]
Stop.
You're under arrest!
[Steve]
Whoa! Hey, hey, hey.
[grunts]
[officers shouting]
["El Fuereño" continues
with lyrics in Spanish]
[siren wailing]
[officer]
Freeze! You're under arrest!
[officers shouting]
[grunting]
[song ends]
[judge]
Mr. Manchester, please rise.
The State has proved
beyond the defined burden
that you committed
the crime of robbery
with a dangerous weapon.
I'd like to take in
consideration
your service to this country
in the armed forces
and the impact of your children
losing a father.
Now, I know
you got everyone fooled
thinking you're a nice guy,
but I know you're a menace.
Although you're only
being tried for one robbery,
we know you've done many more.
And so the prosecution
has requested
that I issue a single count
of felony kidnapping
for each victim
you locked in the freezer.
Let the record state that
on the 4th of February, 2004,
you're hereby sentenced
to 180 months
for each of the three victims,
for a total of 540 months
or 45 years
in the North Carolina
Department of Corrections.
Mr. Sheriff,
he is in your custody.
[gavel bangs]
This concludes this case.
[gallery murmuring]
[lawyer whispering]
[indistinct chatter]
[cell door rattles, clanks]
[phone line ringing]
[line clicks]
[Becky over phone] Hi, Daddy.
I really missed you.
Miss you, too.
I miss you a lot.
Hey, did you get the letter
that I drew
the big ol' house on it?
No.
Well, maybe
it hasn't arrived.
Ask Mama.
Mom says
she'll save the letters.
When I'm old enough,
I can read them.
No, no. That is not...
that is not right.
These letters are for,
they're for right now.
[Talena] Tell him
we're cutting the cord.
They said
we have to cut the cord.
[Jeffrey]
No, we're not cutting the cord.
[stammers] Who said that?
We went to a meeting for
families with dads in prison.
Okay, well, that's good.
That's really good.
What'd they say there?
That it isn't my fault.
It's your fault.
And to let you go, all the way,
'cause you'll never come home,
even if you say you will.
Look,
that last part is not--
that is very, very wrong.
[recorded voice]
You have 60 seconds remaining.
Hey, can you put
your mom on for a second?
He wants to talk to you.
No. Tell him that
you have to hang up.
Gary's gonna help you
with your homework.
She doesn't want
to talk to you.
She said I have to get off
and do homework.
Gary is going to help me.
Gary? Who's Gary?
Mom's friend.
Huh. Mom's got
a new friend named Gary.
That's-that's fun.
[Talena]
It's okay, sweetheart.
You can tell him.
Um, okay, I'm gonna call you
tomorrow at the same time
I always do, all right?
They said no more calls.
No, no.
Who said that? No.
[Talena]
Hang up the phone.
[Gary]
It's okay, Becky.
You can hang up now.
[Jeffrey] Hang up?
Is that Gary?
Put him on the phone
right now.
[Talena]
Hang up. Hang up.
Put Gary or your mom
on the phone right now,
Becky, okay?
[Becky]
I have to hang up.
Hey.
Listen to me,
I'm coming home.
Tell your brothers
And we don't say goodbye,
'cause goodbye means going away
and going away means
forgetting, and we're...
[click, dial tone drones]
We're-- H-Hello?
Hello?
B... Becky?
[prisoner] Why is you
still thinking about them?
You got to let that go.
Ain't no
getting out of here.
Get that idea
out your head.
[Jeffrey] Every prisoner
wants the same thing:
to get out of prison.
[tools buzzing]
And they think
that the way out
is through a wall
or over a fence.
But the guards
got that covered.
The way out of prison
is through the people.
Prison was
just another building
full of systems
and routines.
Keep the routine,
and the guards
won't get suspicious.
If you're nice enough,
if you're useful,
they forget
you're in there
for a reason.
And when they stop
watching you,
you can start
watching them.
You smell that?
Smells like you're leaking.
How 'bout
checking it out
for me.
Yes, sir.
See if you see
anything.
Yeah.
Doesn't look too bad
just yet.
I don't know--
it'll probably get you back
to where you're going.
All right.
Well, come on out of there.
Yeah, you better
tell your maintenance guy.
You might need a new gasket.
I appreciate it, man.
Yes, sir.
Have a good one.
You, too.
[truck door closes]
[engine starts]
[tools buzzing]
[whistling a tune]
[door opens]
[tools buzzing]
[truck back-up alarm beeping]
[truck engine rumbling]
Yeah. Straight back.
Two boxes.
[Jeffrey] Yep.
Two benches.
Yes, sir.
All right.
Shut her down.
She's all yours,
Mr. Cummings.
Thank you, bud.
Hey, smells
like you fixed it.
[chuckles] Good catch.
All right, drive safe.
All right,
have a good one.
[truck door closes]
[engine starts]
[engine idling]
[low, indistinct chatter]
[chatter continues]
[brakes hissing]
[engine rumbling]
[tires screech]
[brakes hiss]
[truck door opens]
Jesus.
Phew.
[belt jangles]
[zipper whizzes]
[sighs]
[belt jangles]
[zipper whizzes]
[engine starts]
[dog barking in distance]
[insects chirping]
[Jeffrey laughing softly]
[Jeffrey whispering]
Yeah.
Yeah, pedal, pedal, pedal,
pedal, pedal.
[Jeffrey laughing softly]
[grunts]
["S'Cudjo" by Zé Manel playing]
[phone ringing]
Hello?
[Jeffrey over phone]
Steve. It's me.
Jeff, Jeff, what the fuck
are you doing calling me, man?
You all over the goddamn news
and shit.
Look, I got to get
out of the country.
I'm thinking, like,
Brazil or Venezuela.
Somewhere with a beach
and no extradition.
[Steve]
God, you sound fucking crazy.
[stammers]
I know. I'm sorry.
Don't do no stupid shit
like go see your family.
Hide. All right?
Okay. Okay. I'll hide.
Don't call back
for another month.
All right,
I'm-a call you in a month.
And don't call
my motherfucking phone again.
You got it? A'ight.
[click, dial tone drones]
Steve?
St--
[sighs]
[cart wheels rattling]
[music playing
over vehicle stereo]
[light music playing
over speakers]
[Mitch] You.
[girl] A lot.
[Mitch]
A lot? We have-- Yep.
What do you want?
[girl] A monkey.
A monkey?
[kids chattering]
Wait a minute.
[boy] Turtle.
[Mitch] Turtle.
What--
and what do you want?
[girl] Candy.
Candy?
We got a lot of candy.
Uh, um, sir,
we're closing here
in ten minutes.
Sir?
Yeah, no problem.
[toys beeping, chirping]
I got you.
[toy beeping]
[toy phone ringing]
[toy gun firing]
[indistinct chatter
over speakers]
[toy laser gun firing]
[door creaks]
[door closes]
[panting]
[shoes squeak on toilet]
[grunting]
[door opens]
[indistinct
police radio chatter]
[door closes]
[indistinct police radio
chatter continues]
[officer over radio]
Zero, three, six,
five, nine, eight, two.
[footsteps approaching]
[indistinct police radio
chatter continues]
[officer] Bathroom's clear.
[door opens, closes]
[exhales]
[Mitch over speakers]
Attention,
Toys "R" Us customers.
Our store will be closing
in five minutes.
So, if you are not a toy
or an employee,
please bring your purchases
up to the front.
Whether you are a kid
or a parent
or an uncle or a friend
making a dream come true,
it is time
to make your choices
and meet us
at the register up front.
If you can't decide tonight,
don't worry.
We promise you
we will be here tomorrow,
just as long as you promise us
to never grow up.
[exhales quietly]
[clattering]
[toy squeaks]
[shoes squeaking softly]
[doors creaking]
[unzips backpack]
[exhales]
[news anchor]
Jeffrey Manchester, also known
as the Roofman, escaped
from Brown Creek Prison
earlier today.
Tonight, he's still
out there somewhere.
[reporter] Authorities
discovered Manchester,
who was serving 45 years for
armed robbery and kidnapping,
was missing this afternoon...
Ha.
...during a routine head count.
Correction officers
do not know the method
or exact time
of Manchester's escape...
They still don't know
how I got out.
...but believe he may still be
in the Charlotte area.
No, no, no. I'm-I'm long gone.
[Scheimreif]
We believe he fled
sometime between 12:00 and 4:00
this afternoon.
He's a very smart individual.
Super intelligent.
Probably genius level.
But he's also
an absolute idiot.
We believe that the suspect
could be armed.
And he has a history
of violent behavior.
What?
[reporter] Police are asking
if you see someone
who looks like Manchester,
please call authorities
and do not confront him.
[birds chirping]
[busy chatter]
[chair creaking]
[Jeffrey exhales]
[chuckles]
Okay.
All right.
Yeah.
[chuckles]
Password:
one, two, three, four,
five, six.
[mutters]
Whoa. Yeah.
[Jeffrey] Most guys,
when they escape,
get caught
in the first few hours.
They go as far as they can
as fast as they can.
[knocks]
And that never works.
The trick is to stop.
Find a place
no one will look.
["Free" by Ultra Naté playing]
[mutters]
[Jeffrey] Sometimes,
the best hiding places
are in plain sight.
A place where people are
too preoccupied to see you.
So I kept quiet as a mouse.
But not at night.
I owned the night.
♪ Where did we go wrong? ♪
[reporter]
The manhunt for the Roofman
enters its third day.
[Jeffrey] People
have short attention spans.
After a while,
they get bored.
I figured I had to
be quiet for about a month,
give or take.
[reporter]
Still no leads from police
on the whereabouts
of escaped convict
Jeffrey Manchester,
as the manhunt enters
its eighth day.
[Jeffrey] One time,
when I was in the 82nd,
I spent 30 days
in the woods
surviving off of
rainwater and grubs.
Your body doesn't need much
to keep going.
It's your brain
that you have to
take care of.
If you can make your brain
imagine a better place,
it can get you
through anything.
Just pick any place
but where you are.
Like a beach on an ocean.
A place where
your kids can visit
after everyone else
forgets you.
[reporter]
Nearly two weeks
since Jeffrey Manchester
escaped
from Brown Creek Penitentiary.
Police have set up
roadblocks,
concerned Manchester
may still be in the area.
Sergeant,
I'm with Channel 6 News.
Jeffrey Manchester's
still missing.
Do you think he could be
in Charlotte?
[Scheimreif]
He might've kept moving,
but we're not gonna give up
on the possibility
that he still might be
hiding out here
in Mecklenburg County.
And when he tries to run,
we'll be ready.
Good luck.
♪ Never trust another ♪
♪ 'Cause they're all out
to getcha ♪
♪ We have to live
in this world together ♪
♪ 'Gether ♪
♪ If we open up our heart,
love can finally start ♪
♪ Come on and try ♪
♪ Now's the time ♪
♪ 'Cause you're free ♪
♪ To do what you want to do ♪
♪ You got to live your life ♪
♪ Do what you want to do ♪
[shoes squeak]
♪ Do what you want ♪
♪ Do what you want to do ♪
[song fades]
[grunts]
[Leigh over headphones]
One quick question.
[Mitch over headphones]
Uh, yeah.
[Leigh] Okay. I just
wanted to talk to you
about my hours.
[chuckles]
Um...
I need every other weekend off.
[Mitch]
I'm confused.
First you ask me
for a job,
and now you're asking me
for time off.
[Leigh]
Well, you know,
I'm a team player...
Yeah.
...but, um, I'm also a mom.
I know.
Okay. Well...
I do.
Uh...
You-you reminded me.
I got a divorce
six months ago, so...
it's really hard for me to
balance everything right now
with work and my girls
and my ex.
Oh, come on. [mutters]
The custody situation is:
They have, you know,
one weekend him,
one weekend me.
I don't want to bore you
with my personal problems.
Good, good. 'Cause I
don't want to be bored
by your personal problems.
If this is
a Toys "R" Us problem,
then I'm interested.
But personal problems
belong on personal time.
[clicks tongue]
Thank you, Leigh.
Got to get back to payroll.
Work, work, work, work,
work, work, work.
Good to see you.
[Jeffrey] What a dick.
Thanks, Mitch.
Okay.
[door closes]
[Mitch] Unbelievable.
Yeah, you're
an unbelievable dick.
I know you're a mom.
You mentioned it before.
Mom card. Unbelievable.
[stammers]
[Jeffrey]
Dollar sign, U,
C, C, E,
dollar sign, dollar sign.
That's the dumbest password
I've ever...
I've ever heard of.
"$ucce$$."
[computer chimes]
Heh.
[mouse clicking]
[clicking tongue]
[goofy voice]
We found Leigh.
Saturday.
Goodbye.
Boop, boop, boop, boop, boop,
boop, boop, boop, boop, boop.
[pops lips, clicks tongue]
You have the day off now.
[pops lips]
Voilà.
[news theme plays]
[announcer]
The news starts now.
[news anchor] More than
30,000 folks are expected
to crowd into town.
[reporter] ...came up with
the idea "Babe Wash."
And the bikinis do
bring in the business.
[reporter 2] The biggest
celebrations of the Fourth
take place in the skies
right behind me.
[Jeffrey]
People get bored
with last week's news.
Pretty soon,
they can't even remember
why they know your face.
Even cops lose interest
unless you really piss 'em off.
Everybody forgets you
eventually.
[fireworks whistling
and popping]
Except people
who really love you.
[fireworks continue popping]
I couldn't get to
the people who love me now
without hurting them.
The only place
I might ever see them again
was somewhere else
and some other time.
The first step was
getting out of here...
[pliers click]
...to get there.
[phone line ringing]
[Michelle]
Hello?
Hi. Um...
Wh-- Is, uh--
May I, may I speak to Steve?
Please?
Sorry, who is this?
Oh, this is a friend.
Well, I mean, this is...
Oliver. His, uh, his cousin.
[chuckles] I was--
I'm doing this little...
little cross-country trip,
and, uh,
he was, he was expecting me.
I was supposed to visit.
Mm. Mm.
He didn't say anything
about a visit.
And I didn't know
he had a cousin.
He must have forgot
to mention it, I guess.
Um... [stammers]
Who am I sp--
who am I speaking with?
Oh, I'm his girlfriend.
What is this about, though?
'Cause I'm in the middle
of something, so, uh...
His girl-- okay, great.
Could I talk to Steve now?
He isn't here.
Okay, well,
should I call back
in, like, a...
like, an hour or so?
Uh, well, he's not gonna be
back until December 1st.
Where does anyone go
till December?
He's in Afghanistan.
He's not in Afghanistan.
We got back two years ago
from Afghanistan.
Well, he took
a six-month contract.
Um, but he asked me
to take messages for him.
Is there something
that you want me
to tell him if he calls?
Yeah, uh...
tell him that, uh,
Cousin Oliver is gonna stay
with relatives in the area
until he's back
on December 1st
for a really
important meeting.
Okay, I will tell him that.
And, uh, I will see you then,
too, I guess.
Cousin Oliver.
[laughs] Bye.
[line clicks]
[dial tone drones]
[line ringing]
[Becky over phone]
Hello?
Stop tickling me. Just a sec.
Hello? [giggles]
[giggling]
Gary is crazy.
Gary!
[Gary laughing]
Who is it? Hello?
[giggling] Gary!
Hello?
Gary.
Who is this?
[Becky continues giggling]
Jeff, is this you?
If you call here again,
I'm gonna call the cops.
Do you hear me?
[Jeffrey crying softly]
We've moved on.
And you need
to move on, too.
[Becky chattering]
Don't call here anymore.
[line clicks]
[dial tone drones]
[panting softly]
[sighs]
[clattering]
[clattering continues]
[Elmo toy laughing]
[Elmo]
That tickles.
[laughing]
Oh, boy, that tickles.
[distorted]
Elmo wants to play.
[laughing]
Let's play.
[overlapping chatter]
[Elmo 2]
Oh, boy, that tickles.
[Elmo 3]
Elmo love you.
Elmo wants to play.
You're Elmo's sweetheart.
That tickles.
Let's play.
Elmo love you.
Oh, boy, that tickles.
[distorted,
overlapping chatter]
Let's play.
[Elmo singing "The ABC Song"]
Elmo love you.
Elmo loves his ABCs...
[humming]
[sputters]
Hey, Leigh.
[Mitch]
Otee-Otee-Otis.
[murmurs]
Hey.
[Otis]
Hey, Mitch.
You're just the man
I want to see.
[time clock clicks]
Cool.
You, uh...
you like Peanut M&Ms, right?
Yeah.
Yeah?
[Mitch over headphones]
'Cause we're missing a lot
of Peanut M&Ms.
You have any idea why?
No.
[Mitch]
What's wrong?
[Otis] Nothing's wrong.
[Mitch]
Seem nervous.
[Otis] I'm not.
[Leigh]
No.
[Mitch]
No?
No. Not happening.
You can't talk to him
like that.
Okay. You know, we are missing
half a dozen boxes out there.
And I just thought-- boop--
they got to be hiding
somewhere-- boop.
[Leigh]
I am so sorry.
[Mitch]
Oh, God.
He cannot talk to you that way.
[Mitch]
I'm the bad guy now.
[Leigh] Hey. You got to
stick up for yourself.
Okay? Or he's just
gonna get worse.
I'm not big
on conflict, so...
Yeah.
Okay, well,
we'll-we'll work on that.
[Otis]
Cool.
[Leigh] Listen, Mitch,
you really hurt
Otis's feelings,
and I think
you should apologize.
[Mitch] I'm sorry.
[Jeffrey mumbles]
[Leigh]
Well, that's a good start.
[Mitch chuckles] Okay.
[Leigh] You know,
people respect kindness
in a leader.
[Mitch]
Mm.
[Leigh]
W-With that in mind,
I wanted to invite you
to my church.
Crossroads Church.
It's, uh, just across
the interstate.
Uh...
Have you been?
Not very churchy.
Okay, well, I'm in charge
of the toy drive there,
and it got me thinking,
here I am,
working in a toy store
of all places,
and you haven't even donated
one toy to my toy drive.
Well, we sell toys here.
We don't give 'em away.
Okay. What about
all those returned toys?
Perfectly good ones
that we can't sell.
We run a business here,
Leigh.
Okay.
Well, you can still come.
You know,
all people are welcome.
Even if they're mean
or aren't quite ready yet.
So you can come, bring
a big bag of toys, or not.
[Jeffrey chuckles]
You'll be welcome.
But bring the toys and you
could be a good guy for once.
Don't you want to be
a good guy?
Come on, Mitch! Be a good guy!
[Mitch]
Okay.
[sighs]
[mutters]
Is that garbage?
Uh...
Huh?
Do you want me to put that
in the garbage for you?
It's just toys for the...
Uh, I heard
there was a toy drive.
Well, it's right
this way.
It's o-- I'll just
leave 'em here. It's okay.
[chuckles]
I'm not gonna walk
all the way down there
in these heels.
It's very nice
of you.
Here you go.
Thank you.
[laughs]
Oh, it's too heavy
for me.
[chuckles]
Got to bring it on
in there.
Come on, I'll show you
where the toys go.
Where do you want me
to put 'em?
You can bring 'em
right in here.
Service
is about to begin.
[light gospel music
playing inside]
[Pastor Ron]
Anyone that feels
alone out there...
[music continues]
...just come on down here.
[speaking quietly]
'Cause you belong here.
We're all sinners here,
which is why I ask my wife
sometimes to sing this tune.
♪ In times of despair ♪
♪ I think about
The good things
That you've done ♪
[congregation whooping
and murmuring]
♪ Ooh, and though
You're not there ♪
♪ I sometimes ask myself ♪
[Pastor Ron]
♪ Is anyone? ♪
[Eileen] ♪ Is anyone? ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Oh ♪
[choir joins in]
♪ It's so hard being human ♪
♪ With all the troubles ♪
♪ In sight ♪
♪ But somehow I know ♪
♪ I know, I know,
I know, I know ♪
♪ Everything's gonna
Work out all right ♪
♪ Hey, yeah ♪
♪ But somehow I know ♪
♪ Everything's gonna
Work out all right ♪
♪ Hey, but somehow I know ♪
♪ Everything's gonna
Work out all right ♪
[song ends]
[cheering and applauding]
[Eileen]
Hallelujah.
[lively chatter]
Wow. Somebody is
very hungry, huh?
Big appetite there, huh?
[mouth full] Sorry.
[laughs] Please.
I haven't had food this good
in so long. [chuckles]
No, that's great.
Big food for a big guy.
Yeah.
Now, you can't sneak
out of here
without saying hello
to the pastor and his wife.
No.
It's against the rules.
No, I would never.
I would never.
I'm Eileen.
John. Z-- uh, Zorin.
John Zorin.
Yeah, I haven't seen you
around the area before.
I noticed you,
obviously, in the,
in the-the row there.
Where are you from?
You new to the area?
Yeah, uh, I'm-I'm...
[sighs] I'm just new
to this place
and, really, everything.
You know, it's, um...
All of this is
really just, you know...
Every-Everything here
is just new for me.
I'm-I'm down
from New York City.
That's
a walking man's town,
I mean, if ever
I've been-been to one.
That is
a walking man's town.
That is correct.
I bet you go through a lot
of pair of sneakers, don't you?
[laughs] Everyone does.
Right? Do you go through...
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, my. You've--
You got very small feet
for a big guy.
No, I actually have
large feet. It's just,
I put on the wrong shoes,
and I don't know,
I think these are, like,
nines in women's.
And I'm sorry, I would never
wear sneakers to church.
I-I'm really sorry.
You know, I-I would like
to introduce you to someone.
I'd like to introduce you
to Leigh Wainscott.
She runs the toy drive here,
and I heard you gave
such a generous donation.
I know she'd like
to thank you for it.
You know, she looks a bit busy
over there, actually, Eileen.
She's having a serious
conversation with her daughter.
[chatter fades]
Now?
[Pastor Ron]
Yeah.
[Eileen] We can.
Yeah. Okay.
You made such
a great donation.
Okay. Yeah, sure.
Yeah. Hey, hey.
Okay, great.
Uh, Leigh. Hey, Leigh.
Leigh. Hey, Leigh.
Come, come say hi
to our mystery man.
Okay.
Come on.
Yeah.
This is our all-star Leigh.
She is the backbone
of everything
that is good going on
in this church.
She does the outreach,
does the meals,
does the toy drive,
she...
I really don't know how
she does it all, but she does.
And this is John...
Zorin? Zorin from New York.
Oh, New York.
That's far from here.
Yeah, a little bit, yeah.
[Eileen] So, John-- he made
a very generous toy donation.
Oh, that's so kind
of you. We...
Couldn't have come
at a better time.
No, I-I mean, um,
I really like Christmas
and-and birthdays,
uh, and just
gift-giving time.
[laughs]
I mean, I don't know.
[stammers]
I just love kids.
You have kids, John?
Well...
You have a family,
or are you single?
I'm, uh, just officially
divorced, that's all.
[Pastor Ron]
Oh, I'm sorry, John.
Not-not all marriages
work out, right?
That's-- that is true.
But to answer your question,
I do have kids.
I have two little
monster boys,
and I got a little girl
that is my best pal.
That's sweet.
And, um... Yeah.
But they're in New York,
and I'm here working.
And what-what-what do you--
what do you do for work?
Well, I... [sighs]
I-I work for the government,
um, but I can't exactly
talk about it.
It's, uh, it's classified
and all that silliness.
[Eileen] Oh.
Well, John Zorin from New York,
our New York spy.
No! No, no.
[laughter]
Definitely not that.
I like that.
Okay, okay.
Well, can I ask you,
can we count on you
to join us next Sunday?
Yeah.
Well, and also
this Wednesday.
Oh. Wow. Yeah.
What's-what's Wednesday?
Uh, I run a singles dinner,
and this week's gonna be
at a Red Lobster.
I love a Red Lobster.
I mean,
not just the seafood.
Those cheese biscuits...
Mm-hmm.
I mean, yeah.
I-I mean,
are you gonna be there?
[Eileen]
Hmm. Leigh?
You think you're gonna join us
for our first single dinner?
Well, I never thought of myself
as being a single,
but, sure, yeah,
I-I'll-I'll go.
[Eileen] Okay.
Yeah, I'll-I'll be there.
Count me in.
[Eileen] Okay.
[Kami] Good to see you.
Thank you so much.
Thank you for joining us today.
Really appreciate it.
[Jeffrey]
I liked being John
better than I liked
being Jeff.
See you on Wednesday.
Wednesday. Yes, ma'am.
John was a good guy.
People liked him.
Leigh seemed to
like him, too.
But there was no way
a girl like her
was gonna really fall
for a guy
in women's running shoes
and a Spider-Man T-shirt.
[groans]
Also, I really needed
to see a dentist.
Living on candy is
hard on your teeth.
[entry bell jingles]
Good afternoon.
How are you?
Good, sir.
[bag unzips]
See what you give me
for these.
Uh, how about
ten apiece? 300.
Yeah, I'll go 300.
Okay, let's do that.
Yeah, deal. Yes, sir.
M.O.D. on number 29.
14 cavities. That's a lot
of cavities for an adult.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I just have a bit--
naturally, I guess,
a bit of a sweet tooth,
and I've had access
to a lot of really good candy.
Just haven't been able to...
Open your mouth
wide, please.
...s-stop. Okay.
[whirring]
[laughter, lively chatter]
[pop music playing]
Look at those.
Oh, wow. [chuckles]
[Kami chuckles]
[excited chatter, clapping]
[Jeffrey]
Hello. [chuckles]
Hello, ladies.
[women] Hi!
Hi.
How is everyone?
[chuckles]
Good.
Oh, okay.
[women chuckling]
I thought this was
a singles brunch,
not a supermodel brunch.
[laughter]
Ooh. [laughs]
[Kami] You could always
squeeze in down here by us.
[laughter]
Well, we wanted
to welcome you, John.
[Kami] Yes.
Welcome, welcome.
Am I the only guy
that's gonna be here today?
[laughs]
[women] Yes.
Uh-huh. Yep. You are.
Turns out to be so, yes.
Right. Okay.
Yes. I hope we're not
overwhelming for you.
Oh, no, no, no,
I'm actually-- I-I'm
liking it very much.
Okay, good.
I love having
so many new friends,
especially beautiful friends.
Um...
Ooh.
[woman]
Sweet one.
So, John, I understand
you work for the government.
What kind of work?
I-I would love
to get into those details,
but I'm undercover, so, um...
[women oohing]
Oh, that sounds mysterious.
No, I can promise
it's not that mysterious.
It's really quite boring.
[chuckles]
I never knew there was
an intelligence unit
here in Charlotte.
Oh, are you law enforcement?
I'm retired now,
but I was.
Wow. That's amazing.
[high-pitched gasp]
Am I, am I, uh...
[laughter]
Am I arrested?
How does this work?
I don't want to
make you upset.
[Kami]
You're embarrassing
everyone, Sally.
He did not come here
to be interrogated.
No, no, no,
I actually really like it.
I feel a lot safer
with her here.
Um, but-but yeah.
Um, there's intelligence
just about in every major city.
We just don't advertise
that much, yeah.
Well, if he's undercover,
why's he at a singles dinner
at Red Lobster?
[overlapping chatter]
That's a fair question.
Well...
I-I can...
That is, that is a question
that is not classified.
I am here possibly looking
for the next Ms. John Zorin.
[laughter, applause]
Oh, please. Oh, please.
[Jeffrey stammers]
See, but there-there
is a problem, though.
I'm having a bit of an issue
that there's just
too many beautiful choices here
to choose from.
[excited chatter]
No, I'm-I'm sorry.
I should not have said that.
My mom always told me
do not compliment a woman
on her beauty because
it makes her self-conscious.
Um, always start
with their shoes.
[laughter]
Speaking of.
Hold on a second.
Let me get
under this table.
[laughter]
Excuse me.
Got some high boots
down there.
Stilettos at brunch.
All right, girl.
[laughter continues]
Okay, okay.
[Kami]
It is getting hot in here.
[lively chatter]
No, no, no, no.
[Leigh]
That was really fun.
Look, I don't get out much,
so this was fun for me.
Me neither.
[chuckles]
You sure made their day.
They made my day, truly.
This is my car.
I mean, I've never been...
This is you? Ooh, a Subaru.
Yeah.
I like it.
All right,
I'm-I'm getting
my courage up.
Um...
I have two questions
to ask you.
Two? Just two?
Yeah.
All right.
Let's hear it.
Drumroll. Give me
the first one. Go.
Um, you're gay, right?
What? I'm what?
You're gay.
Gay? No.
Yeah.
[laughs]
What?
Are you kidding
right now?
No, I...
No, I mean, look,
I don't have
anything against gays.
I love gays,
but, like, I'm--
no, absolutely not.
You just...
What made you think
I was gay?
You just seem like
one of the girls.
Or, like, you seem
to love women's shoes.
No, that's not
what that was.
[laughs]
All right.
Uh-uh.
All right, well, that--
if that's a no,
we can go straight
to question two.
Okay. Uh, yeah.
I guess, hit me.
[chuckles]
Um...
Um, would you like
to go out with me?
On a date?
Okay.
Wow, you're
a very forward person.
I, uh...
Um, yes, I would,
I would very much--
really, very much--
like to go out
on a date with you.
[laughs]
I don't know, yes.
Yes is the answer
to that.
All right.
Okay.
I'm free, um,
next Saturday morning?
Perfect.
I'll pick you up.
Where do you live?
[sputters]
I live in
a really boring, uh,
government building
that's non-disclosed
to the public.
How about this?
Uh, let's meet
at Freedom Park.
Saturday morning,
8:00 a.m.
Sounds like a,
like a-- uh, well,
sounds like a date.
It's a date.
So it's a date.
Okay. Bye.
All right. All right. Sorry.
Hey. [laughs]
You were shaking,
and I was going...
But don't get...
There's a car.
[gasps] Oh, shit.
[laughs] Okay.
All right. Yep.
All right,
that was awkward.
Okay.
See ya.
Bye!
[Leigh]
It's hot.
[Jeffrey]
It's hot. [grunts]
Wow.
You're in
really good shape.
Thanks, girl.
[both laugh]
My ex, Jeffrey, he...
Yeah?
What?
You said Jeffrey.
Yeah. That's my ex's name--
Jeffrey.
Got it, right.
Yeah.
His name
was Jeffrey?
Yeah. He was in...
Wow.
...horrible shape.
Like, we had no...
No...?
It's just been
a long time.
Oh, okay.
But we're nothing alike.
Good to know.
Yeah, I-I like people.
He didn't talk.
He just read war history novels
on the toilet.
[laughs]
What?
Mm-hmm.
[gags]
N-No, Jeffrey,
that is gross.
[laughs]
Right? [laughs]
[gags]
He loves his books,
but when it comes to
time for the girls
or homework
or driving lessons,
just doesn't show up.
Stressful.
I just think you need
a little bit more fun
in your life,
to be honest.
[stammers]
Okay.
Do you want to go
back to mine and have
some fun right now?
What?
Really?
Mm-hmm.
Yes. Very much, yes.
I would very much--
yeah, mm-hmm.
Okay.
Mm-hmm. Yeah. Now?
Yeah.
All right.
Told you I wasn't gay.
[laughing]
Shut up.
[Jeffrey]
Tell me about your daughters.
[Leigh] Their names
are Dee and Lindsay.
Dee's 11.
She's pretty sensitive
and creative.
She's like...
I don't know.
She-she hasn't let me
cut her hair
since she was a baby.
She's one of those kids.
And then Lindsay's 16.
She has a sign
on her door that says,
"Emotionally unavailable."
[laughs softly]
She also just
got her learner's permit
but refuses to drive,
even though
she wants her freedom,
so that's where we're at.
Oh, is that right? [laughs]
Well, I'm a good driver.
If you want me to teach her,
I-I'll happily do it.
[laughs]
We just met.
That's a good point.
That's a... [stammers]
Yeah, I know.
Um, I just love kids, so...
Okay, well, maybe...
maybe you could
meet 'em sometime.
You know, like, maybe
you could come over for...
for pizza one weekend,
maybe?
Like a pizza party?
Can we have a pizza party?
Like a pizza Saturday?
[laughs]
I haven't been
out of the house,
let alone on a date, okay?
Okay.
In a very long time.
Mm-hmm.
Um, I... I don't know
if my girls are ready
for, you know,
M-Mom to be dating
just yet.
I get that.
We can still have a pizza party
and just make it
just totally normal.
I'm just a friend from church,
you know,
that happens to be
a government spy.
[laughs]
A non-gay one.
You know,
a non-gay government spy
that just comes over
and wants to, you know,
have pizza with you
and your daughters.
You know, just make it normal.
Okay.
You're-you're not normal,
John,
but...
[snickers]
[laughing]
I like you.
You know what's not normal?
Hmm?
You just look like this
all the time?
[scoffs]
Looking inviting.
[laughing]
[Jeffrey mumbles playfully]
[Leigh squeals, laughs]
[birds chirping]
[sighs]
[bags rustling]
[knocking on door]
[Leigh] Oh.
He's here. Okay?
[door opens]
[Jeffrey]
Hello.
Please come in.
Wow, that's
a lot of food.
Girls,
this is my friend John.
John, these are my girls.
Hey, girls.
Uh, hi.
I'm-I'm John Zorin.
I'm your mom's good friend
from church.
You must be Dee.
That's short for Delia?
Yeah.
Yes.
You must be Lindsay,
and that's short for...
That's not short for anything
at all, actually. [laughs]
Look, I've heard
so much about you guys.
Uh, and one of the things
that I have heard,
is that you, Dee,
happen to be a huge fan
of Zelda, like I am.
Is that true?
Yeah.
Is that right?
Good, 'cause I got you
this Link doll.
[laughs]
And another question:
[whispering]
Have you played Four Swords?
No.
It is so amazing,
and it comes with
this special controller
that I'll teach you
how to use later
until you can whup my butt,
which you'll probably be able
to do really quickly
''cause I hear you're,
like, a Zelda master.
[laughs]
Thanks.
Yes. Zelda worked.
One down.
Lindsay, for you,
I have an assortment
of very angsty teenage music
for your listening pleasure.
[laughs]
[Leigh] Thank you?
No, thank you.
Nice to meet you,
John Zorin,
Mom's friend from church.
Where are you going?
I have homework.
[sighs heavily]
[Jeffrey] It's okay.
[laughs]
Maybe next time.
Okay?
[Leigh groans]
All right? Don't worry.
[sighs]
I, uh, also happened
to have gotten you something,
Miss Leigh.
Oh.
[Leigh]
This is all so sweet.
[chuckles]
I'm sorry about Lindsay.
I-I thought this might be
hard for her.
[Jeffrey]
Yeah. No, and, look,
I understand that.
[Dee]
This one has to go on top.
[Jeffrey]
Yeah, the top, top part.
And this one
has to go...
[Jeffrey] But wait,
where's the light...
[Dee]
Wait, you got to connect.
[Jeffrey]
Oh, the click.
[chuckles]
I love the click.
And this one
has to go on that.
[Leigh] Dee?
Yeah.
It's 11:00.
Past 11:00.
Oh, come on,
let us finish this. Please?
Please?
She's, like, the best builder.
We're like 20 pieces away
from the end.
[Dee]
Yeah, please, Mom.
So close.
Another time, okay?
[Jeffrey]
Okay.
I had the best time
with you.
Okay?
Yeah.
[grunts]
[Jeffrey]
Can I see you again?
I'd like that.
Yeah?
Yeah.
So, if it's late,
I'll just come and, like,
tap on your window?
Oh.
[snickers]
I don't know if I'm a...
"tap on the window"
kind of girl, John.
No?
All right, how about I just
knock on the front door?
Okay.
[piano playing
"I'll be Home"]
[Pastor Ron]
♪ I'll be home ♪
♪ When your nights
are troubled ♪
♪ And you're all alone ♪
[choir] ♪ Ooh ♪
♪ When you're feeling down ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ You need some sympathy ♪
♪ There's no one else around ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ To keep you company ♪
♪ Ah ♪
♪ Remember, baby ♪
♪ You can always ♪
♪ Count on me ♪
♪ I'll be home ♪
♪ I'll be home
I'll be home ♪
♪ I'll be home ♪
♪ Wherever you may wander ♪
♪ Wherever you may roam ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ You come back ♪
♪ I'll be waiting here
for you ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Ah ♪
♪ I'll be here ♪
♪ To comfort you ♪
♪ And see you through ♪
♪ I'll be home
I'll be home ♪
[Leigh] Goodbye, Halloween.
♪ I'll be home ♪
Turkey time.
[song fades]
[Leigh]
Don't hit the light.
[Otis] I won't.
Yeah, maybe next year
we should get
an inflatable Otis.
[Otis mutters]
[clicks tongue]
Hey. I-I'm not
stepping in this time.
Okay? You got to do it.
You got to do it.
You got to punch the bully
in the nose, you know?
[keyboard clicking]
[knocking on door]
My man, Otis.
Yeah.
Yeah. I need to tell you
something, Mitch.
Whoa, okay.
Yeah.
I mean-- okay. What?
Um...
[breathing heavily]
What?
Uh...
[Otis stammering]
[Jeffrey] Please say it.
No, I'm sorry.
Um, I'm just...
What, what?
Uh, I was, I was, um...
Say it.
Otis, come on.
I...
[Jeffrey] Just say it.
I wanted to tell you I-I...
What?
I sweeped up the stockroom
like you said.
Okay, is that it?
Yeah.
No. No.
[Jeffrey]
My mom used to tell me
be careful what you touch.
She said that moving one grain
of sand changes everything
in the whole universe.
I think people call it
the butterfly effect.
That just one butterfly
flapping its wings can
make a hurricane
on the other side of the world.
And before we know it, we're
banging into each other's paths
and changing what happens.
[Leigh]
Are you sure you want bangs?
Sure.
It's a big change.
Thing is about bangs,
there's only about
one in a thousand people
that actually look good
with bangs,
but good news is I think that
you might be one of them.
[laughs softly]
Oh, God.
[Jeffrey]
No one notices the butterfly
flapping its wings
until everyone
feels the storm.
I knew a storm was coming.
I knew if I stayed
in one place too long,
eventually someone
would recognize me.
I knew I had to leave.
I just didn't want
to go alone.
[Jeffrey chuckles]
You think you could
ever just move somewhere else?
Like a beach or something?
Start over in a new place?
I don't know, John.
I-I need to come back here,
you know?
We could take the girls.
Just pack up and go.
Mm. That's...
No, I can't do that.
I can't do that.
My life is here,
John.
["Don't Speak" by No Doubt
playing over headphones]
[Mitch]
♪ You're letting go ♪
♪ And if it's real ♪
♪ Well, I don't want to know ♪
[Mitch grunting rhythmically]
♪ Don't speak... ♪
[water running]
[Mitch singing in distance]
♪ Stop explaining ♪
[water stops]
♪ Don't tell me
'Cause it hurts ♪
♪ Don't speak ♪
♪ I know what you're... ♪
[grunts]
♪ I don't need your reasons ♪
[muffled]
♪ Don't tell me
'Cause it hurts ♪
[song continues
over headphones]
♪ Our memories ♪
♪ They can be inviting ♪
♪ But some
Erotically enticing ♪
♪ Writing ♪
♪ As we die ♪
♪ Both you and I... ♪
[singing fades]
♪ Stop explaining ♪
♪ Don't tell me
'Cause it hurts ♪
♪ No, no, no, no, no ♪
[gasps] What the fuck?
[yells]
What? Oh, my God!
[Jeffrey yelling]
Oh, my God!
[Jeffrey continues yelling]
[door opens]
[alarm wailing]
[grunting]
[panting]
[alarm continues wailing]
[grunting]
[clattering]
[grunts]
[alarm continues wailing]
[sirens wailing outside]
[siren whoops]
[sirens wailing]
[alarm continues wailing]
[Mitch over headphones]
Oh, my God,
there's a lot of you.
He's-he's big. He's naked!
He came at me.
[officer]
Sir, is he still here?
[Mitch]
I don't know.
I heard the-the outer...
the alarm door went off.
[officer]
So he may have gone outside?
[Mitch] Uh, yes.
[officer]
Charlotte Police!
[officer 2] Charlotte Police!
[officer]
Charlotte Police!
Police department!
[indistinct shouting]
[siren whooping]
[officer]
The alarm was going off.
When we came back here,
the door was ajar,
so we really believe
he went out this way.
[Mitch] We could watch
the whole thing, Officer,
'cause I know how to... press
"play" on this thing, so...
[Scheimreif] Mitch?
Yeah?
The good news is
you have surveillance cameras
all over the store.
[Mitch] Yes. Yes.
[Scheimreif]
Bad news...
is none of them
were recording.
You need
to fix that.
Now, besides
the naked guy,
have you noticed
anything strange
happening around here?
Uh, uh...
Uh, well, we're-we're missing
a lot of gaming inventory.
[mutters softly]
What's a lot?
A substantial amount.
[Scheimreif] You're gonna
have to get some real security
in here, Mitch.
[reporter]
Workers at this Toys "R" Us
are prepping
for the holiday rush,
but store manager
Mitch Haggin says
he did not expect to see
what he saw this morning:
a strong, very tall, naked man.
[Mitch over TV]
Uh, a-a naked guy ran at me.
I think he was gonna kill me,
and I ran away,
locked myself in my office.
[reporter]
When I asked if the naked man
would scare off
holiday shoppers,
Mr. Haggin said he was hiring
round-the-clock security.
We have a really good security
system here now, for sure.
Families can feel safe.
This is a safe place
to come for Christmas.
[Leigh]
I think it looks great.
[TV clicks off]
Hi.
We're almost
ready to go.
[Pastor Ron]
Lord, we want to thank you
for this wonderful food,
and we want to thank you
for the gift of family. Amen.
[all]
Amen.
Happy Thanksgiving.
[happy chatter]
[Eileen]
So, Leigh.
Yes?
Why don't you tell us all
that story about the naked man.
[chuckles]
Oh, it-it's nothing, y'all.
It... it was cold outside,
and a homeless man
needed to take a shower.
Yeah, but what if
he's also a killer?
He's...
Stop being overdramatic.
He's not a killer.
[chuckles]
Your mom's totally right.
He's definitely not
a killer.
You don't know that,
John.
Well, if he was a killer,
he'd have killed him, right?
Uh, the paper said today
that there was $10,000
in video games stolen.
Mm.
[Randy] I don't know
if that's a coincidence or not.
[Eileen]
That is a lot of money.
[Lindsay]
Well, I don't know, Mom.
Maybe you should quit.
You have
a master's degree,
and I don't think
it's worth the risk.
It seems scary
over there.
I mean, that's not
the worst idea,
I guess.
I like my job.
[Randy] Wait. Hold up.
Earlier, you just made it seem
like it wasn't dangerous.
So, if it's not dangerous,
then-then why does
she have to quit so suddenly?
[Pastor Ron] Yeah.
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
Uh, did I, did I say
she had to quit?
I don't think I did,
actually.
I think I was just agreeing
with Lindsay down here.
I was just saying here
that Lindsay
actually has
a great idea.
If she wants to quit,
then she would
have more time
with her girls.
Yeah.
[Pastor Ron]
Now, everybody,
let's not get too serious,
because, uh...
[laughing] I just think
it's kind of funny.
I imagine the guy,
he's just going to work,
just a normal day,
and then he sees a naked guy
running around
inside his toy store.
[laughter]
[Kami] Makes me want
to get a job there,
actually.
[laughter]
Oh, Kami, bless you.
Yeah, I just think
it's really funny,
that's all.
I don't think
it's funny, Ron.
I-I think it's sad.
I mean,
someone's so desperate
they had to bathe
in a toy store sink,
while we eat
and laugh about it?
I mean, maybe we aren't
Good Samaritans.
[Eileen]
Mm.
[Lindsay] Maybe you aren't
making the best decisions.
Excuse me, ma'am?
Choosing to work there
while Dee and I
are home alone,
waiting for someone
to pick us up
to take us places?
Like, we...
Whoa, whoa.
If we're being honest,
you're old enough
to drive yourself.
[Lindsay]
I don't have a license.
I told you
I would teach you.
Okay?
[Lindsay] I can't even
sit in the car with you.
And now that Dad's not here,
you bring around this weirdo,
and we're supposed
to just accept it?
I-I hope the sex
is worth it.
[gasps]
[Pastor Ron]
Hey, hey, hey.
[Leigh]
Lin...
[Leigh clears throat
softly]
Sorry.
[chair scrapes on floor]
[Kami whispers]
Our church.
[Pastor Ron] Yeah.
[quiet chatter]
[phone ringing]
[Pastor Ron]
Wow.
[phone continues ringing]
Hello?
[Jeffrey over phone] Uh, hi.
[whispering]
Um, this is Cousin Oliver.
I was just calling
for Steve.
It's 7:00 in the morning.
[Jeffrey]
Uh, it's also December 1st,
and we had a conversation
a few months back
that I should call back
on December 1st.
Yeah, you just call back.
He's sleeping.
Okay, well, can you
just wake him up for me?
Um, just tell him
it's Cousin Oliver.
All right?
It's urgent.
Baby.
Mm. Mm.
It's your cousin.
It's Cousin Oliver.
[groans] Tell him I'm asleep.
[muttering]
Motherfucker. Goddamn.
He says...
We can do it Sunday.
...he's asleep and that
you should come
see him next Sunday.
Next Sunday.
Okay, great. Is he
still in Fayetteville?
No. No.
It's the Twin Pines Motel.
Twin Pines. Okay.
Room 204.
204. I got it.
[Steve] And don't be
a fucking dumbass
and take the bus.
He says don't be a fucking
dumbass and take the bus.
He wants to know
if you got a car.
[Jeffrey] Yep. Tell the sarge,
uh, I'll take care of that
and I'll see him on Sunday
as scheduled.
[phone beeps]
[dishes clatter]
H-Hi. Morning.
You didn't tell me
you had to take a trip.
You weren't supposed
to hear that.
[laughs]
Okay.
Look, it's not a big deal.
I just have to go
and just check in.
That's all.
Okay.
Mwah.
Morning, Lindsay.
Good morning, Leigh.
Good morning, Dee.
Everybody want to say
"good morning"?
[Dee] Morning, John.
[Jeffrey chuckles]
All right, who wants
to apologize first, hmm?
No? You?
Come on, guys.
[stammers]
Nobody has anything
to say to each other?
Look, families fight.
That's fine,
but they also make up.
Come on.
I'm sorry for the way
I've been acting, Lindsay.
[knocks on counter]
Great work.
I shouldn't have said
the thing about sex
in front of Dee.
Mm. Yeah.
And...
And? You got it.
And I need a ride
to Doug's.
Nope. That wasn't...
You aren't getting
a ride anywhere.
Do you have any idea
how much you embarrassed me
last night?
I embarrassed you?
John, will you drive me?
You do not get to abuse him
and then ask him for favors.
[Jeffrey] It's okay.
I-I don't mind driving her.
No, stay out of this, John.
See, he doesn't mind.
If she wants to go somewhere,
she can learn to drive.
I'm not driving in that car
with that stick shift
with you ever.
Well, then I guess
you'll never go anywhere again!
[Jeffrey]
Okay, time-out. Time-out.
Ever!
I'm sorry, can I ask my mom
to drive me places
'cause she's my mother?
[Jeffrey] Okay, stop.
I have an idea, okay?
I have an idea. Hear me out.
It's a great idea.
We need a beater.
What even is a beater,
John?
["Little Drummer Boy"
by Jim Nabors playing]
♪ Come, they told me ♪
♪ Pa, rum, pum, pum, pum... ♪
[Jeffrey speaks indistinctly]
[salesman] That's a nice ride
right there, huh?
Classic 1999
with very low mileage.
[Jeffrey] Yeah?
[salesman]
Great color, too.
Awesome family car.
[Jeffrey]
It's automatic.
[salesman]
It is automatic.
Great price.
You guys
want to try it out?
Yeah.
Got the keys right here.
Look at that.
[sighs]
It's nice seats, right?
You know, modern cars
just don't have the same feel.
This is kind of like
the golden era.
The '90s. [sighs]
You know, just... [stammers]
They don't make modern cars
like this anymore, you know?
Yeah.
These-these are like sofas.
You guys buckled up?
[Leigh] Yeah, yeah.
Any cops around here ever?
Oh, no, no.
Nobody's gonna stop you here.
Just gonna push it
just a little bit.
[engine revving]
[tires squealing]
[salesman chuckles]
Okay.
[girls laugh]
[chuckles]
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
It's got some horsepower.
Okay.
All right, all right.
Got a nice V-6...
[engine revving]
Okay. Okay.
[yells nervously]
[tires squealing]
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hey, sir! Sir!
Watch out!
Here we go.
Oh. Oh! Oh!
[tires squealing]
[girls scream]
[scream] Fuck!
[girls laughing]
Fuck! Slow down!
Slow down!
Slow down! It's a used car!
Slow down! [scream]
Slow down! Slow down!
[tires screeching]
♪ I played my best for him ♪
♪ Pa, rum, pum, pum, pum... ♪
[yelping]
[Jeffrey and girls laughing]
You guys okay?
Motherfucker!
Yeah?
All right, good.
[laughing]
What's wrong with you, man?
[laughs] Calm down.
No, no, get out.
Calm down. No, no, no.
Get out. Get out!
I'm driving us back.
Lindsay, Lindsay. Stop.
Calm down.
Lindsay, get up here.
You drive. You in the back.
No, maybe
she shouldn't drive,
John.
No. No, she's a kid!
She can't drive!
It's busy here. It's busy.
No, she can drive.
Listen.
No, give me the keys
right now.
No, no.
Stop, stop.
Calm down, okay?
How do you teach a kid to swim?
You throw them in the water.
Right?
If you want her to drive,
we got to let her drive.
[Dee] Oh, yeah.
Go, Lindsay.
[salesman]
Does she even have a license?
[Jeffrey]
She has her permit.
[Leigh] No.
[salesman] No, you cannot
test-drive with a permit.
Look, listen,
I'm gonna purchase this car
if the young lady approves,
and I'm gonna pay cash.
How's that sound to you?
I'll let you hold it.
Come on.
Yes.
Get up here.
You're driving.
All right.
Seat belts. Safety first.
All right, this is not
a manual transmission.
This is an automatic,
so it's so much easier.
You can just forget about
your left foot.
It's all right foot.
So put your right foot
on that brake right there,
the big pedal.
Yep, push it all the way in.
All the way in. Real firm.
Okay, now you're gonna
take your right hand,
you're gonna pull that
towards you and down to "D."
Perfect. Now let it go.
Back at two.
All right. We're not
gonna worry about the gas.
You're just gonna ease
your foot off the brake
and we're just gonna
move forward, and that's it.
All right? Take a big breath.
You got this. [chuckles]
[Dee laughing]
[laughing]
You got it. Come on.
You got it.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's good.
[Jeffrey] Nice.
[Leigh] Good one.
All right, family.
I always
love to take pictures
of my happy customers,
if you guys don't mind.
All right.
Big smile.
[camera clicks]
One more, one more.
[camera winding]
Now, let's pretend your dad
almost crashed the car.
[Dee laughing]
[camera clicks]
All right.
[camera winding]
[all chuckling]
Hey, great,
great stuff, guys.
Thank you very much.
You're a better driver
than him.
[laughter]
That's true, actually.
I felt really, really safe
with you, so good job.
[growls playfully]
Oh, I'm glad.
Thank you, John.
Congrats, man.
Will you girls wait
in the car
while I talk to John
for just, like,
a minute? Here.
Okay.
[keys jingling]
We got a beater.
[laughs]
Yeah, we got a beater.
Yeah.
[girls laugh]
I have to say it.
I did not like that driving.
Okay.
I'm sorry. I know.
I shouldn't have done that.
Yeah.
But Lindsay was a really,
really good first-time driver.
Wasn't she?
She was great.
Yeah.
She did so good.
And-and-- I don't know--
I think she's starting
to like me.
They both like you.
They really like you, okay?
I like you.
Just... just need to slow it
down a little bit, okay?
Okay.
And we don't need
so many things, John.
We just want you.
Just be you. Be normal.
I promise. The most normal.
Okay.
You take your trip,
and when you come back,
we'll have a-a few
normal nights, okay?
No more stunt driving,
I promise.
Okay.
[girls making
kissing noises]
[chuckling]
[Leigh]
Oh, gosh.
[giggling,
making kissing noises]
I love John.
[Jeffrey]
Oh, my God.
The car. I love the car.
It's the perfect car.
See you back at the house.
Okay.
[knocking]
Hi.
Uh, Cousin Oliver.
[dog barks]
Here for Steve.
Oh. Mm,
it's a little early.
[chuckles]
Hey, Steve?
[Steve] Yeah?
Cousin Oliver's
here.
[dog barking]
Hello, dumb dog.
Yeah, I knew you'd show up
at the crack of dawn
if I ain't give you
a time.
Welcome home, Sarge.
Man.
All right, you...
[grunting] Oh, man.
Yeah,
that is enough.
Yeah.
Damn, you look clean
for a motherfucker
that's on the run.
I'm trying. I'm trying.
Where you was
hiding out at,
church?
You know
I can't tell you that.
Seriously,
where you hiding out at?
No, I can't tell you that.
You don't want to know that.
You ain't got no contact,
right?
You ain't
talking to nobody?
No, no.
Okay, 'cause you know
if you are,
I can't help you.
No, why would I do that?
You good?
I'm good. I'm good.
Keep your eyes on me,
then.
Why you keep
darting them around?
I'm not darting them.
I'm looking right at you.
You sure
you're all right?
Look.
Okay.
["Loyalty" by the
Tim Terry Experience playing]
[Steve] We gonna
need to change that hair
before we take the photo.
Uh, baby, what you think?
Wig? Dye?
For-for his hair.
I think we do a wig.
Yeah. Don't worry, Jeff.
You'll still be you.
But cuter.
Like Brad Pitt.
Ugly-ass Brad Pitt.
[Steve]
Oh, my God.
Baby, are you serious
about this?
I'm-I'm...
[stammers]
This is a panty dropper.
Oh, my God.
Baby, come on.
Okay.
Oh. [groans]
You got to be
fucking kidding me, baby.
[Michelle]
Say hi, baby.
Wow.
Baby, th-that's...
that's a good one.
That's good, right?
Yeah.
This one feel good to you?
Mm-hmm.
Mm-hmm?
Feels like you could be
this person for a while?
Mm-hmm.
You ready?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Stop with the damn smiling.
Fuck you doing?
Just... normal face.
No, yeah, serious.
It's like a...
it's your passport, you know.
You're not allowed to smile.
One, two, three.
[camera beeps, clicks]
[whirring]
[Steve]
Read this shit. Study it.
All of it.
All right?
It's gonna be the new you.
You're Kenneth Owen Griffin.
Born July 7, 1974,
from Lumberton, North Carolina.
Now, I'm-a get
all your documents.
Don't worry about shit.
Transfers, records--
I'll have it all done, A to Z.
Okay. What-what are you
thinking, like 5K?
Oh, no, it's gonna be
a lot more than that, man.
More than that?
How-how much more?
You think I don't know
what you doing, huh?
You probably got a girlfriend,
don't you?
What? No.
Yeah, you do.
Yeah, you not good
at this shit.
Good at what shit?
Being a criminal, nigga.
Let me tell you something.
Good criminals
are cold, calculating.
You understand?
Now, you got
the calculation down,
but, man, you just... goofy.
The price...
it's gonna be 50K.
All right?
50? 50?
Yeah.
Hey, you a lot of risk, man.
Can you do it?
Okay. Yeah.
How you gonna do it?
I'll get it.
Well, if you're thinking about
using a gun, do me a favor.
Stay the fuck off the TV.
Roofman, you understand
what I'm saying?
Don't do anything stupid.
[engine revving]
[grunts]
[panting]
Ow.
[exhales]
Okay.
Shit.
What the...?
[panting]
[crickets chirping]
Shit!
[shouts]
Stupid idiot!
[panting]
[alarm blaring]
[groans]
[alarm continues blaring]
[door rattling]
[hammer drops on floor]
[grunts]
[alarm ringing]
[Mitch]
90% of our annual sales happens
in the next two weeks.
Think about that.
There's gonna be
a lot of money coming in,
and we need to be ready
for it.
Considering
our recent setbacks,
I think we're doing
pretty good.
You should be proud.
Come on.
Come on, guys.
Come on. Come on.
But the ball game
starts now.
[Mitch]
We're beefing up security
so the store is safe
and families feel safe
in the store.
Right on schedule.
Because if our customers
have a good Christmas,
then so do we.
You are so punctual, my friend.
I like it.
Your job is to sell toys.
[Mitch]
It's gonna be a little bit
heavier this time around.
[straining]
Yeah, getting a lot
of these lately.
It's good for your arms,
muscles there.
[Mitch]
We're gonna open early
and stay open late every day
this Christmas season,
and that includes
Christmas Eve.
I posted the new schedule.
Now, I know some of you
are gonna have shifts
they don't want,
but there's no exceptions
or changes.
You show up when your name
is on the schedule.
Now, let's have
a happy Christmas.
Let's do this for the kids.
[clapping over headphones]
Come on. Back to work.
♪ Oh, our Father is
The maker of Mary ♪
["Happy Christmas" by Byron Lee
& the Dragonaires playing]
♪ And Mary is
The mother of his Son ♪
♪ The Son is a blessing
From the Father ♪
♪ So let's hear
Thanks and praise ♪
♪ Sing happy Christmas ♪
♪ To you ♪
♪ You... ♪
[Lindsay laughing]
Nice hat.
You look like
a Christmas supervillain.
Yeah, I am
You're driving, though.
I'm driving?
You are driving.
Okay.
Holy shit,
you got so much stuff.
[laughs]
Mom's gonna freak out.
Yeah, she's gonna freak out
with joy.
[laughs evilly]
[bells jingling]
[upbeat music playing
over speakers]
♪ Coming back for everyone ♪
♪ Christmas is
coming back again... ♪
Hi, Mom.
Okay.
[Jeffrey]
Perfect timing.
Everyone's ready to go.
Mwah.
[Leigh]
Hey, guys.
I can't go
to church tonight.
Why not?
I have to wake up
super early.
I have a shift tomorrow.
[Jeffrey]
Then I have good news
for you.
Mitch called,
and he's gonna be
a nice guy
and let you sleep in.
Mitch called?
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
Uh, said 10:30.
10:30?
[chuckles]
Yeah.
10:30 to 4:30,
I think he said.
Why? [chuckles]
I, uh... I don't know.
I mean, maybe he knows
that you have a family
and he wants you to be able
to spend the holidays
with them.
[upbeat music playing
over speakers]
♪ Coming back
For everyone... ♪
[Lindsay chuckles]
[Leigh sniffles]
Mm-hmm.
Hey, Mom.
Hey. [chuckles]
I love you.
[Lindsay] I love you.
[Leigh]
I love you.
[church band playing
"No Room At The Inn"]
[Eileen]
Come on into the manger.
♪ Well, she said
There was no room ♪
[choir] ♪ No room ♪
♪ No room ♪
♪ No room at the inn ♪
♪ Well, well
The time had fully come ♪
♪ For the Savior
To be born ♪
♪ But they told her
There was no room ♪
♪ No room ♪
♪ No room at the inn ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey ♪
♪ According to the Word ♪
♪ Oh, yes ♪
♪ There was a virgin girl ♪
♪ Hey, hey ♪
♪ Oh, yes ♪
♪ Mother of Jesus ♪
♪ Wandering round that night ♪
♪ Oh, yes ♪
♪ She was trying
To find a place ♪
♪ For the Savior to be born ♪
♪ But they told her
There was no room ♪
♪ No room ♪
♪ No room at the inn ♪
♪ I said there was no room ♪
♪ No room ♪
♪ No room at the inn ♪
♪ One more time
There was no room ♪
♪ No room ♪
[fading]
♪ No room at the inn ♪
♪ I said the time
Had fully come ♪
♪ For the Savior
To be born... ♪
[takes deep breath]
[grunts]
[sighs]
Otis, back to work. Come on.
Clean that nursery, would you?
Like I told you to.
Okay.
["Sleigh Ride"
by The Ronettes playing]
[panting]
[Mitch] Hello, sir.
[guard] Hello.
Mr. Money Man,
Mr. Money Man.
[breathing sharply]
♪ Just hear those
Sleigh bells jingling... ♪
[Jeffrey] Good morning,
Toys "R" Us employees!
Hello. This is the police.
[employees screaming]
You guys, you know you got
an alarm going off back there?
Everybody, this way.
You're coming with me.
Little faster.
[employee] Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. He has a gun.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Please keep your hand away
from your gun, sir.
Get on, get on your stomach.
You two, come here.
No one's gonna get hurt if
everybody just does what I say.
On your stomach. Otis, here.
Zip-tie everybody up.
Otis, come on.
Uh...
Jesus Christ.
Mitch, zip-tie everybody up.
Okay? Get on your stomachs,
eyes down.
[Otis] Okay.
Wh-What did I say?
Come on.
On your stomach.
Get down.
Don't do this right now.
Hey, hey.
What did I say?
[employees screaming, sobbing]
Shit.
That wasn't my fault.
[employees whimpering]
He's a bad listener.
[employees sobbing,
breathing heavily]
[Mitch]
This is not happening.
Everybody, take a breath.
Mitch, give me one of those.
Thank you, sir.
[zip ties fastening]
[Mitch muttering]
Sorry. Sorry.
[grunting]
Okay.
[Mitch] Sorry. Sorry.
[Jeffrey] Come on, Mitch.
Let's get a hop on.
Let's go.
It's gonna be okay.
Sorry. Sorry.
[groans]
Guys.
Everybody, just calm down.
I'm sorry about this.
Mitch, get the keys.
Come on.
Let's go to the safe.
No, there's no money here.
There's no safe.
You think I don't know
that there's a deposit that you
take to the bank every Tuesday?
Huh? Come on, please.
You're okay.
[Mitch whimpering]
Eyes down. Eyes down.
I'm sorry about this, guys.
It'll be all over in a second.
Come on.
You do this every day.
Calm down.
Come on. Here we go.
Good job.
Eyes down.
[whimpers]
Just... find the key.
Oh, God.
[Jeffrey]
Eyes down out there!
Yes. Okay, put it in.
Oh. Okay.
Put it in the safe
and open it.
Take the bag out.
Put it down.
I need you to take
the ink bomb out.
If I do that,
it'll blow up everywhere.
Not if you do it quick.
Zip it right back up
really fast, okay?
Okay.
Okay, good.
[gasps]
[screaming]
Oh, God.
[Mitch whimpers loudly]
Goddamn it.
["Adeste Fideles"
by Vic Damone playing]
[employees whimpering,
sobbing]
[Otis]
He needs an ambulance!
You said you weren't
gonna hurt anyone,
but you hurt him!
He needs an ambulance!
And you're just a bully!
[sobbing]
You're just a bully!
Otis?
♪ O come, all ye faithful ♪
[crying]
I can't see.
[Otis crying] He need...
he needs an ambulance.
♪ Joyful and triumphant... ♪
I guess it's obvious
I'm just a pushover, huh?
All right, Otis.
Fine, I'm calling 911, okay?
♪ To Bethlehem ♪
[line ringing]
♪ Come and behold him ♪
[operator]
911. What's your emergency?
♪ Born the king of angels ♪
♪ O come, let us ♪
[Leigh gasps]
♪ Adore him ♪
Shit.
♪ O come
Let us adore him ♪
♪ O come, let us ♪
Shit!
♪ Adore him ♪
♪ Christ the Lord ♪
[alarm blaring]
[grunts in frustration]
♪ Sing... ♪
Charlotte Police!
Police department!
♪ Sing in exultation ♪
Oh, oh, wow. Okay.
Wait a second.
♪ Sing, all ye citizens... ♪
You were
calling him names.
[Otis laughing]
He had a gun,
and he was calling him
a bully.
[laughing]
Oh, man.
♪ Glory to God ♪
♪ In the highest, glory ♪
[fading] ♪ O come
Let us adore him... ♪
[officer] Did you see
any part of his skin
or any other clothing?
[Leigh] Um, I could tell
he was a white man, yeah.
Did you see his eyes?
Mm-mm.
[Steve] This is
fucking fantastic, Jeff.
You a fucking nut,
you know that?
It's fucking great.
Baby, you see this?
[Michelle]
Yeah.
[Steve]
Okay, let's see.
This is your
North Carolina-issued
driver's license, all right?
That's your passport.
Notarized birth certificate.
You got your check stubs
from your last job.
Oh, and there is your ticket.
You leave at 11:00 p.m.
out of Charlotte.
Now, what you're gonna do
is a layover in Miami,
and then you're gonna fly
to Barranquilla.
From there, you're gonna
take a little bus
and it'll have you in Venezuela
before the weekend's out.
Looks like I got
everything I need
in case I decide
to go tomorrow.
"Decide"?
You already made
your decision, man.
What you talking about?
I mean, you can't expect me
to go on Christmas, right?
Can't I just stay awhile?
I'll just lay low.
That's not a choice
you have, Jeff.
You got to leave tomorrow.
I got people waiting
on you, man.
I got a security guy in Miami.
He'll be at line three.
You got one shot, man.
11:00 p.m. tomorrow.
Don't miss this shot.
All right?
Baby, let's get this,
uh, wig on him.
[Michelle]
You bet.
One more thing
I was thinking about.
Saw on the TV
there was some shit
about a armed robbery.
I don't know nothing
about that.
[Michelle]
I need your thumbs.
[sighs]
You know, you got
to cover your tracks, Jeff.
Yeah.
Everything you touch.
I need you to really think
about who you talked to,
who talked to you,
who knows your voice.
I'm over a cliff for you, man.
You understand that, right?
Yeah.
So, nothing?
No doctor's visits?
Uh, I went to the dentist
and got some cavities filled.
But that's it.
Okay. You ain't get no X-rays?
No, I got X-rays,
but I gave 'em a fake name.
Okay. Well, it don't
really matter
if you gave 'em a fake name
if they got your teeth, Jeff.
[sighs] All right. Yeah.
Look, I'll take care of it.
Any messes you made,
you clean it up.
Then you go straight
to the airport
and wait for your flight.
No getting on the news.
No good-byes to anyone
you said hello to.
That means no postcards,
no calls. No none of that.
["Auld Lang Syne" by Byron Lee
and the Dragonaires playing]
Shit, we had a good run.
You know?
You know, after all this stuff
calms down and, like,
I get settled over there,
do you think you could tell
some people where I'm at
and they maybe could...
visit me sometime?
No, no, no.
It's none of that, man.
Nobody coming to see you, Jeff.
You're starting over.
You're on your own now.
[softly] Yeah.
[traffic passing]
[liquid splashing]
[explosion]
[glass shattering]
Oops.
[engine revving]
[ringtone playing]
[Jeffrey sighs]
[ringtone stops]
[ringtone playing]
[ringtone continues]
Hello?
[Leigh]
John.
I was just about
to call you.
Is everything okay?
I've been calling you.
Where are you?
I'm driving.
Well, actually,
I just pulled over.
Are you coming
to Christmas dinner?
The girls have been
asking for you.
Yeah. Yeah, of course.
Yeah, I wouldn't miss it.
Want to meet us at 5:00?
At home?
At 5:00? Yeah, yeah,
that sounds good.
Yeah. I'll be there.
[Leigh sighs]
You there?
Are you okay?
I can hear you,
I can hear you breathing.
I love you, John.
I love you, too,
Leigh.
I'll see you at 5:00.
[line clicks, beeps]
[airplane approaching]
[sighs]
[jet engine whooshing loudly]
[birds chirping]
[engine shuts off]
[car door closes]
[car door opens]
[vehicle engine revving]
[dog barking in distance]
[knocking]
Leigh?
[dog continues barking]
[Jeffrey]
Merry Christmas--
Police! Lay down!
[officers shouting]
Get on the ground!
Get down!
On the ground! Get down.
Get down.
Don't move.
Do not move.
Doing good. Don't move.
Do as we say
and you won't get hurt.
You understand me?
I got him. Nuh-uh.
Don't move, dickhead.
[siren whoops]
Don't fucking move.
Drama's over.
What's your name?
[officer over radio]
[Jeffrey over radio]
I think you know my name.
[officer]
What's your name?
[Jeffrey]
Jeffrey Manchester.
[officer] PID. Target.
[Scheimreif] We got him.
We got the Roofman.
[indistinct
police radio chatter]
[officer]
He almost made it.
Let's move.
[indistinct
police radio chatter]
Come on.
Search his ass.
He's a tricky motherfucker.
This way. Come here.
Search him good.
[indistinct
police radio chatter]
[Jeffrey]
I probably let myself
get caught.
Or maybe I just couldn't leave
without saying goodbye.
They threw the book at me.
Gave me 384 more months.
That means by the time
I get out of here,
I'll be an old man.
[door closes]
Gave me a lot of time
to think about my life.
Everything.
When I was out there
in the world,
I wasn't thinking
of the things
or people that I was
putting at risk.
Now that's all
I think about.
We all like to go
back in time to imagine
how things
could've gone differently
if we made
different choices.
Like right now.
I was imagining
what it would've been like
if I never committed
all those crimes
and lost my family.
Or if I got to
keep on living
with Leigh and her girls
forever.
Sure, they'd boss me around
a little
and make me go to church.
But they'd laugh
at my dumb jokes
and forgive me
when I was on the wrong part
of cold and calculating.
Or something.
[honks softly]
I started to realize
that all those people I loved
didn't need me
to give them so many things.
They just needed me.
My time.
And now that's all I have.
Time.
[Becky] I got four A's.
[Jeffrey]
You got all A's?
[Becky]
Yeah.
Even in math?
Becky,
I'm so proud of you.
[Jeffrey]
It all could've gone
a different way, for sure.
But it didn't.
It went this way.
Hey, buddy.
And that was okay with me.
'Cause in here, I...
I can't hurt anybody
anymore.
Yeah. I'm...
I'm where I'm supposed to be.
[prisoner]
You ever think about it?
What?
[prisoner] You know,
breaking out of this place.
[chuckling]
No. No.
Mm.
I'm...
This is my home now.
[prisoner 2]
You know, I have to admit,
brother, like,
that love story part
was really good.
I am curious.
You ever see Leigh again?
[door buzzes]
[quiet chatter]
[sighs]
[Jeffrey laughs softly]
Hey.
Hi.
Should I call you Jeffrey?
Just another jerk Jeffrey
in your life, I guess. Yeah.
How's Lindsay and Dee?
They're okay.
Yeah.
Did Dee keep her bangs?
She did.
[softly]
Yeah.
[breath trembles]
I'm sorry.
[crying]
I'm so sorry that I hurt you.
I'm sorry
I couldn't protect you.
You don't have anything
to be sorry about, Leigh.
You don't.
You didn't hurt anybody.
You just told the truth.
Yeah.
I was really angry at you.
I was most angry
at how you hurt the girls.
[sniffles]
But that's not the way
I think about it now.
Okay?
I think about it
as an adventure.
We had a lot of fun.
[sniffles]
We're thankful.
Well... [clears throat]
maybe I'll come visit you
sometime.
Gonna tap on my window?
[both chuckle]
Maybe I'll just knock
on the door. [laughs]
[sniffles]
[crying softly]
[reporter] The Roofman
has returned to rob again,
overnight cutting his way
into this McDonald's
on the intersection
of Wilkinson and Main.
[man] Just to look
at what he's done,
it appears
he's very intelligent.
Um, it's just that
he also likes to commit crime.
[reporter 2]
Holes cut into the roofs,
workers told
to get into the coolers,
but no one was hurt.
In fact,
the suspect was nice.
[man 2]
Very polite person.
He always makes sure
that the employees,
before he walked them
into the refrigerator,
that he has them
put on their coats
so that they'll stay warm.
[reporter 3]
This was an earlier
composite drawing of Roofman,
always wearing a mask.
The owner here
refused to comment
on all details
of the robbery,
referring calls to
the McDonald's corporation.
But he's also robbed
Burger King and Blockbuster...
[reporter 4] Police caught him
with $9,000 in cash,
allegedly stolen from
two McDonald's restaurants,
the first in Gastonia,
the second in Belmont.
The suspect
almost got away,
until a worker
at this Belmont McDonald's
saw which way he ran
and then called police.
I interacted with Jeffrey
on the robbery that happened
in the McDonald's in Belmont.
The whole time,
he was saying,
"I'm so sorry. You guys
are the good people.
I'm the bad person."
He was a nice fella.
He, uh, he was real nice.
He didn't, uh...
he didn't come across as, uh...
you know, come up,
talk junk, you know.
Or, "Why am I here?"
Nothing like that.
You know, he...
he was a nice fella.
He's an incredible liar,
um, pretty much
about everything.
Everybody thinks,
"Oh, he's such a hero
"because he-he gave the toys
to the children."
Well, the toys are stolen.
[Pastor Ron Smith] As far as,
like, having an inkling
to maybe
there's something there,
no, I didn't have
any kind of inkling.
He was a nice fella.
He got involved in our church.
[reporter 5]
But now that the pastor knows
John is really
Jeffrey Manchester,
the escaped convict accused
of sticking up Toys "R" Us
and torching
a dentist's office,
how does he feel?
My belief is that, um,
as a church,
you got to stand with somebody.
Doesn't mean that you agree
with what they did.
The Roofman,
or the Rooftop Robber,
I-I never heard
anything about that.
It was--
I was oblivious to anything
until after my relationship
with Jeffrey,
and then he was captured.
Then it just seemed
to be everywhere.
[scoffs] Never thought that
would happen to my office,
him trying to burn it down
to-to hide his record.
The whole front area was gone.
In the beginning,
it just seemed to me
he had everything together.
And it's a perfect example
of how greed and money
and bad influences in your life
could change your outcome.
[reporter 5]
Pastor Smith says
he's already visited
Manchester in jail.
He could not believe
that I came to see him,
that, um, that we would
not just be really mad at him
and turn our back on him.
[reporter 5]
Although it was
a church member
who turned Manchester in.
Police captured him
leaving the apartment
of Leigh Wainscott,
the new girlfriend he met
at a church singles event.
I talked to my oldest daughter,
you know, about this,
um, recently,
and, uh, I asked her
to share with me
anything that she remembered,
um, that she could share,
and she just said,
"Oh, yeah,
I remember very well.
"He was, he was awesome,
you know.
"We had so much fun."
And, um...
They didn't have anything bad
to say about him.
Nothing at all.
[music ends]